SHREYANSH **RAVAL**

WEB DEVELOPER







raval201081@gmail.com



Dehgam

Education

SSC

Revaba Vidhyamandir 2018 - 2019 72.67%

HSC

Revaba Vidhyamandir 2020 - 2021 70.28%

BCA

Silver Oak University 2021 - 2024 9.18 CGPA

Language

Gujarati

English

HIndi

About me

I am a Web Developer with nearly one year of experience in building responsive websites. I am passionate about learning and improving my skills, and I enjoy collaborating with teams to solve problems and create userfriendly solutions. I am eager to grow professionally and contribute to new and exciting projects.

Experience

Technical Support Intern

Nov 2022 - May 2023

Sunshine Info Solution

Junior Web Developer

July 2024 - Present

eBranding Studio

Skills

Languages

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

Tools

Git, GitHub, Visual Studio Code, Chrome DevTools

Techniques

Responsive Design, Cross-browser Compatibility, Web Performance Optimization

CMS

WordPress (Theme Customization, Plugins, Content Management)

Technical SEO

Website Structure Optimization Page Speed Optimization Mobile Optimization